Hi my name is Donna and I'm a mother of three. I was going through really tough
times because not only do I work full-time at a very demanding job but I
also have to take care of my kids. One of them even has special needs so I needed
something that would help me. I was very stressed. I was having panic attacks. I
didn't know what to do and so I was very happy and grateful to have met Shree.
Shree helped me get the root cause of what was causing my panic attacks, what
was causing my stress and it has changed my life immensely. Now I am calm, I'm
collected, I can actually stop and think before I was just on the go and I was
just running a mile a minute and it was crazy. My life has changed drastically.
Shree has taught me the ways to calm down and you know just take things in in a
way that's peaceful and calm and it's made my life so much better. I'm a better
mom, I'm a better worker because of it and my job. I mean so much has changed. So
thank you so much Shree. I highly highly recommend his coaching and the advice
he gives and he's changed my life so thank you so much Shree. I highly
recommend him. If you're going through what I was going through.